<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Arun Mathai</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Arun Mathai</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Arun Mathai</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2016 17:51:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Youtube Channels I Like</title>
      <link>/notes/youtube-channels-i-like/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/notes/youtube-channels-i-like/</guid>
      <description>These are the channels I somewhat enjoy watching&amp;hellip;, although I might not be so up to date with them.
If any of the links are broken, please let me know 😁.
Food Stuff  Strictly Dumpling Mark Wiens The Food Ranger  Techinal Stuff  Dave&amp;rsquo;s Garage Strange Parts tripcode!Q/7 Jadi Tsoding Daily Jeff Geerling Computerphile Xah Lee The Linux Channel  Other Random Stuff  Paolo fromTOKYO TABI-IE -quiet night- Tom Scott  Vsauce  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Websites I Like</title>
      <link>/notes/websites-i-like/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/notes/websites-i-like/</guid>
      <description>If any of the links are broken, please let me know 😁.
Personal Websites  Akshay S Dinesh Ravi Dwivedi Sahil Dhiman Abraham Raji Aral Balkan  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I love healthy communities</title>
      <link>/weblog/why-i-love-healthy-communities/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/weblog/why-i-love-healthy-communities/</guid>
      <description>Having a community where you can discuss your ideas, talk with people who have similar ideologies or with people who
have ideolgies poles apart from what you have is truly a privilege.
A safe and healthly community is a perfect place for growth.
For me this was and is FSCI(Free Software Community India) and hopefully will continue to be one in the future.
FSCI is just not about tech and liberation, I feel it is actually about the people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Does a soul exist?</title>
      <link>/weblog/does-a-soul-exist/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/weblog/does-a-soul-exist/</guid>
      <description>I mean all that comes to my mind when I think about the word “soul” is the vague figure of a spirit. (As shown in a few movies)
Other questions which pop up in my mind are:
Is a spirit and a soul the same? And if a soul exists, then where does it reside?
And can a soul be sentient/intelligent/self-aware, If yes then how is it able to think without a brain?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>There really exists no software</title>
      <link>/weblog/there-really-exists-no-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/weblog/there-really-exists-no-software/</guid>
      <description>When I was a small child I used to wonder how computer storage worked and like how I used to click on the delete button and the computer would delete the files magically for me.
I always compared a computer to an actual human and the fact that you could delete files on demand got me crazy cause as a human I could never do that and neither can i do it now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Me</title>
      <link>/contact-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact-me/</guid>
      <description>Feel free to contact me regarding anything via :
Email : me@arunmathaisk.in
Instagram : @arunmathaisk
Twitter : @arunmathaisk
Mastodon : https://mastodon.social/@arunmathaisk
XMPP : arunmathaisk on disroot.org
IRC : arunmathaisk on irc.libera.chat</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
