<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>community on Arun Mathai</title>
    <link>/tags/community/</link>
    <description>Recent content in community on Arun Mathai</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Arun Mathai</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/community/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Am I a Fraud ?</title>
      <link>/weblog/am-i-a-fraud/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/weblog/am-i-a-fraud/</guid>
      <description>Imposter syndrome, a struggle experienced by many, has been a constant presence in my life. Despite my coding skills and technical knowledge, there are times when I can&amp;rsquo;t help but feel like a fraud, merely faking my way through. But I&amp;rsquo;ve come to realize that imposter syndrome is a common phenomenon, and I am not alone in this battle. Through self-reflection and embracing my true abilities, I&amp;rsquo;ve learned to navigate these feelings and grow both personally and professionally.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yummy corporate offerings</title>
      <link>/weblog/yummy-corporate-offerings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/weblog/yummy-corporate-offerings/</guid>
      <description>I would like to believe that I genuinely value the Libre Software principles, ethics, and the whole ecosystem around it. And on the other hand, I do not like nor agree with the business and ethical practices of these huge corporate companies.
But with certain choices, there come certain sacrifices as well. The term &amp;lsquo;sacrifices&amp;rsquo; here can be put to debate but, you get the point&amp;hellip;
So, as an undergraduate student Bacheloring in Computer Engineering, I am displayed with several job offerings from fortune 500 tech companies, several &amp;ldquo;open source&amp;rdquo; projects, some campaigns, and other community/developer advocacy programs that would require me to speak something pleasant about their products and services in exchange of possible recognition or compensation in the form of swags, money or other resources&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I love healthy communities</title>
      <link>/weblog/why-i-love-healthy-communities/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/weblog/why-i-love-healthy-communities/</guid>
      <description>Having a community where you can discuss your ideas, talk with people who have similar ideologies or with people who
have ideolgies poles apart from what you have is truly a privilege.
A safe and healthly community is a perfect place for growth.
For me this was and is FSCI(Free Software Community India) and hopefully will continue to be one in the future.
FSCI is just not about tech and liberation, I feel it is actually about the people.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
